Preliminary Guide to the William Halal papers, 1980-2014 MS2227.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Research Projects - World Technology Network, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Research Projects - Foundation for the Future, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Research Projects - Sohail, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Research Projects - Life Cycle of Evolution-FFF, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Research Projects - Life Cycle of Evolution, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Research Projects - Potomac Institute, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Research Projects - Alternatives to Growth Copies, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Research Projects - Social Accounting Corporate Audit, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Research Projects - DOT, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Research Projects - Department Study, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Research Projects - Laitner, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Research Projects - Shearer, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Research Projects - Future of Technology, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Research Projects - Saturn, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Research Projects - Management Roundtabled, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Research Projects - Mark Satin, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Research Projects - Corporate Models, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Research Projects - Democracy Online Project, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Research Projects - Retina, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Research Projects - Bojes, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Research Projects - Unified Knowlege Management Framework, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Research Projects - GW Forecast Scanning for the Module on Globalization, undated (Box 9, Binder 1)
- Research Projects - Technologies of Consciousness (TOC), 2008-2010 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Research - Social Trends/Wildcards, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Research - Wild Cards, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Research - Medicine, 1994-2006 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Research - Forecasting, 1971-1995 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Research - Relevance Table, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Research - Trend Reinterpretation, n.d., undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Research - Tech and Society, 2002-2004 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Research - Neurotechnologies Study, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Courses Research - Ralph Stayer, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Courses Research - 21st Century Corporation, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Courses Research - Heir to Enterprise, 1994-1997 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Courses Research - Leaders Who Listen, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Courses Research - Anita Roddick, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Courses Research - Walmart, 2005-2007 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Courses Research - Bakery, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Courses Research - Reflections/Misc, 1991-2002 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Courses Research - Post Office, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Courses Research - Bottom Up, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Courses Research - Cheap US Labor, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Courses Research - Funeral, February 2004 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Courses Research - Fast Co., 2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Courses Research - W.L. Gore, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Courses Research - Organizational Intelligence/Knowledge Management (OI/KM), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Courses Research - McDonalds, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Courses Research - Service, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Courses Research - Stakeholders, 1993-2004 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Courses Research - Education, 1997-2002 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Courses Research - Military, 1999-2003 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Courses Research - Government, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Courses Research - Media, 1999-2004 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Courses Research - Gary Hamel, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Courses Research - Convergence, n.d., undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
- 21st Century Economy - Content/Ideas, Reviews, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
- 21st Century Economy - Taylor, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- 21st Century Economy - Publisher, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
- 21st Century Economy - Contents, Intro/Conclusion, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
- 21st Century Economy - Authors, misc., undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
- 21st Century Economy - [Loose Materials], undated (Box 10, Loose-material 1)
- 21st Century Economy - Irving Meeting, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Research Projects ADB - Performance Enhancing Technologies, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Research Projects ADB - Terrorism, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Research Projects ADB - Renesch, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Research Porjects ADB - Biotechnology, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Research Porjects ADB - [Unlabeled], undated (Box 11, Binder 1)
- Research Porjects ADB - ADB, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Research Porjects ADB - [Loose materials], undated (Box 11, Loose-material 1)
- Presentations - Portland, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Presentations - Taiwan, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Presentations - Gas Association, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Presentations - Conference Board, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Presentations - London 106 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Presentations - NASA-Langeley, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Presentations - Ackoff conference, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Presentations - Credit Union Execs Society (CUES), undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Presentations - Freddie Mac, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Presentations - Air Force, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Presentations - Business Intelligence-UK, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Presentations - NSS Group/Department of Defense, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Presentations - Event Managers (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Presentations - Dickinson College, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Presentations - AACSB, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Presentations - CCE, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Presentations - Naval Research Labs/San Diego, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Presentations - CERF, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Presentations - Construction Industry Roundtable, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Presentations - Rodale Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Presentations - Corning, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Presentations - Navy/Newport, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Presentations - GW SAE, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Presentations - HNTB, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Presentations - Lockhead-Martin, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Presentations - American Psychological Association, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Presentations - DOT/FAA/NASA, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Presentations - Brookings, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Presentations - CIO Council, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Presentations - WFS, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Presentations - WFS Houston, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Presentations - Superintendents, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Presentations - SAIC Conference, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Presentations - National Contract Management Association, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Presentations - I.E.K., undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Presentations - AFMA, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Presentations - California Police, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Presentations - [Unlabeled], undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Courses - Faculty Conference, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Courses - Correspondence, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Courses - Chile II, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Courses - Chile, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Courses - Rio, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Courses - Current Issues, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Courses - Organization Networks, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Courses - Systems and Cybernetics, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Courses - Jones, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Courses - Strategic Planning Course, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Courses - Misc. New Courses, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Courses - Grad. Policy, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Courses - Intro Seminar, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Courses - Seminar in Management, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Courses - Independent Survey, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Courses - Technology Culture and Institutional Change, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Courses - Strategy vs. Scenerio Matrix, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Courses - [Untitled], undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Courses - Comp Exams, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Courses - CIBT Case, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Courses - Doctoral Students, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Courses - Strategic Management Survey, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Courses - SP Program, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Courses - Business and Society Course, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Courses - Planning, 1994-2006 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Courses - SOS (Self-Organizing Systems), 1987-2002 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Courses - Leadership/Participation Package, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Courses - Studying IC (Institutional Change), 2002 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Courses - Arch/Conflict-Cooperation, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Courses - Various Conference and Retreat Material, 2009-2013 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Courses - Mission Statement, 1980-1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Courses - Various Topics, 1990-2001 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Courses - Global Order, 1994-2001 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Courses - Information Systems Technology Management Vision and Strategy, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Courses - Ecological Management, 1994-2003 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Courses - Life Cycle of Evolution, 1996-2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Courses - Forecasting Methods, 2000-2011 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Courses - IT, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Courses - Space, 1997-2005 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Courses - Spirit, Values, Etc., 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Courses - Transportation, Homes, 1999-2005 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Courses - Mind, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Courses - Medicine and Biogenetics, 1988-2005 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Courses - Manufacturing, Robotics, Materials, 2003-2005 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Courses - GW Forecast, 1996-2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Book-New Managment - Copy editing, Jacket etc., undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Book-New Managment - New Title, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Book-New Managment - Book Promotion, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Book-New Managment - Book Promotion, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Book-New Managment - Blurbs, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Book-New Managment - Blurbs, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Book-New Managment - Media, 1987-1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Book-New Managment - Book Stuff, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Book-New Managment - Publicist, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Book-New Managment - Promotion-Itineries, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Book-New Managment - TNM, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Presentations/Publications - 21st Century Articles, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Presentations/Publications - Journal Reviews, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Presentations/Publications - Harper/OI Book, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Presentations/Publications - World Bank, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Presentations/Publications - Hi-Tech Exposition, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Presentations/Publications - Global Forum, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Presentations/Publications - EPA/ORD, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Presentations/Publications - Korea, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Presentations/Publications - Toward a Theory of Space Power, undated (Box 15, Binder 1)
- GWU - Emeritus Status, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- GWU - Various Correspondence and Management Science Department Reorganization Documents, 1997-2009 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- TechCast - Website Correspondence with Cynthia (1/2), 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- TechCast - Website Correspodence with Cynthia (2/2), 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- TechCast - Market Survey, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- TechCast - Payment System, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- TechCast - Website Management with Cynthia and Shannon (1/2), 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- TechCast - Website Management with Cynthia and Shannon, 2005-2006 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- TechCast - Source Code CD, n.d., undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
- TechCast - Miscellaneous, 2008-2012 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- TechCast - Student Project, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- TechCast - Website Information (1/4), 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- TechCast - Website Information (2/4), 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- TechCast - Website Information (3/4), 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- TechCast - Website Information (4/4), 2006-2008 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- TechCast - Online Newsletter, 2005-2008 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- TechCast - Keri Program, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- TechCast - Website Changes and Launch (1/2), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- TechCast - Website Changes and Launch (2/2), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- TechCast - Website Mockups, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- TechCast - Publications, 2004-2007 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- TechCast - Experts (E-Commerce Panel, Applications for TechCast Expert Panel) (1/3), 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- TechCast - Experts (E-Commerce Panel, Applications for TechCast Expert Panel) (2/3), 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- TechCast - Experts (E-Commerce Panel, Applications for TechCast Expert Panel), 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- TechCast - Field Editors (1/3), 2008-2011 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- TechCast - Field Editors (2/3), 2008-2011 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- TechCast - Field Editors (3/3), 2008-2011 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- TechCast - Website #5 Changes and Proposals, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- TechCast - L.L.C., 2002-2004 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- TechCast - Company Seal, n.d., undated (Box 22, Object data_value_missing_9b7d7fddfecaeaa298dd0e0824ec19c0)
- TechCast - Logo, 2013 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- TechCast - Social Network Project, 2009-2012 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- TechCast - Student Projects, 2012 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- TechCast - Website Changes (1/2), 2006-2011 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- TechCast - Webiste Changes (2/2), 2006-2011 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- TechCast - 247Tech Radio, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- TechCast - MIMOS, 2010-2011 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- TechCast - American Society of Mechanical Engineers (ASME) External Environmental Scanning Project, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- TechCast - Study for American Council for Energy-Efficient Economy (ACEEE), 2009 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- TechCast - John Sagi and Consciousness, 2009-2010 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- TechCast - Subscribers (1/2), 2007-2011 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- TechCast - Subscribers (2/2), 2007-2011 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- TechCast - Unifusion 2009 Gravitae, 2009-2010 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- TechCast - Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Research, 2001-2011 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- TechCast - Experts Panel, 2008-2009 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- TechCast - Northrop-Grumman, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- TechCast - Relations with King Saud University (KSU) and The Riyadh Techno Valley (RTV) (1/2), 2008-2009 (Box 25, Folder 37)
- TechCast - Relations with King Saud University (KSU) and The Riyadh Techno Valley (RTV) Parameters (2/2), 2009 (Box 25, Folder 38)
- TechCast - Dissolution, 2013-2014 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Director of National Intelligence (DNI) - Scanning (Correspondence and Articles), 2008 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Director of National Intelligence (DNI) - Interviews, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Director of National Intelligence (DNI) - Report, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Director of National Intelligence (DNI) - General Correspondence and Notes About, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Editing - Microvitae Article, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 34)